todaysbigfail.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy | InterWave Studios

Privacy Policy

InterWave respects the privacy of its online visitors and users of its products. InterWave recognizes the importance of protecting any information collected from users and has adopted this privacy policy that guides how InterWave gathers, stores, and uses information from the use of InterWave products and online sites by users. 

This policy is current as of its last revision date. However, please note that this policy may be amended from time to time to reflect changes and additions to the privacy policy. Please check back for the most current version before relying on any of the provisions in this privacy policy.

**Collection and Use of Information**  
By using InterWave's online sites and products, users agree that InterWave may collect aggregate information, individual information, and personally identifiable information, as defined below. InterWave may share aggregate information and individual information with other parties. InterWave shall not share personally identifiable information with other parties, except as described in the policy below. 

"Aggregate information" is information that describes the habits, usage patterns, and demographics of users as a group but does not describe or reveal the identity of any particular user. 

"Individual information" is information about a user that is presented in a form distinguishable from information relating to other users but not in a form that personally identifies any user or enables the recipient to communicate directly with any user unless agreed to by the user in advance of such communication. This information may be used to improve InterWave's products and online sites, for internal marketing studies, or simply to collect demographic information about InterWave's users.

InterWave may use customer contact information provided by users to send information about InterWave, including news about product updates, contests, events, and other promotional materials, but only if the users agree to receive such communications. Except in the cases described below, InterWave will not share personally identifiable information with any third party unless the user agrees to such disclosure in advance. "Personally identifiable information" consists of a user's name, email address, physical address, or other data about the user that enables the recipient to personally identify the user. While InterWave collects personally identifiable information on a voluntary basis, for certain products and online sites, InterWave's collection of personally identifiable information may be a requirement for access to the product or site. Personally identifiable information will be processed and stored by InterWave in databases situated in the Netherlands. InterWave may allow third parties performing services under contract with InterWave to access stored information but such access shall only be to the extent necessary to provide those services. In those instances, the third party will be bound by the terms of this privacy policy. 

Personally identifiable information protected under this privacy policy and collected from users may be done in conjunction with associates under agreement with InterWave. If an associate of InterWave is collecting such personally identifiable information within one of our products or online sites, InterWave will make users aware of this at the time the information is gathered. If a user does not want to provide this information, the user may choose to opt out of providing this information. Additionally, if providing the information is a requirement of usage, the user may decline to use that particular service or product. When possible, InterWave will make a reasonable effort to direct users to the privacy polices of these associates. InterWave's privacy policy does not extend to associates of InterWave.

Furthermore, external websites and companies with links to and from InterWave's online sites and products may collect personal information about users. InterWave's privacy policy does not extend to these external websites and companies. Please refer directly to these companies and websites regarding their privacy policies.

InterWave may release personally identifiable information to comply with court orders or laws that require us to disclose such information

**Children Under The Age of 13**  
InterWave will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person age 12 and under. InterWave encourages parents to instruct their children to never give out personal information when online. Parents who are concerned about the transfer of personal information from their children may contact us at [privacy@interwavestudios.com](mailto:privacy@interwavestudios.com) to obtain a record of any information held by InterWave and have it removed at their request.

Corrections, Updates and Removal of Information  
If you are concerned about the accuracy of personal information maintained by InterWave or would like your personal information removed from InterWave's records, please contact us by emailing [privacy@interwavestudios.com](mailto:privacy@interwavestudios.com) for review, update, or removal of personal information.

**Contacting InterWave**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, or the privacy practices of InterWave, please contact us by emailing [info@interwavestudios.com](mailto:info@interwavestudios.com).

Revision Date: May 8, 2008

* * *
